Timothy Morrise

Full Stack Web Developer looking to apply skills in Javascript/Node.js

Salt Lake City, UT 84103 (801) 560-6195 tmorrise.surge.sh | timothy.morrise@gmail.com| github.com/timothymorrise | https://www.linkedin.com//timothy-morrise

PROJECTS

Screaming At Awards Shows — Full Stack CRUD Website

An app to generate text for a personal ballot for different Film and TV Awards Shows. Uses React/Redux for front-end, pulling from a local Restful API for the Award Show data built with Express and MonogoDB.

Github:

Marquee Salad — 'Nilla Javascript Single Page Site

A minimalist web page that helps theater operators know which letters to pull when changing their marquees. Built using "vanilla" Javascript Github:

Boy Counter Experience—Personal Site that uses the Youtube API

A personal site I built using the Youtube API to populate a page with videos from the web series "Monster Factory." It manages personal data using React/Redux and Flexbox to create a pseudo-blog feed design and navigation.

Github:

EXPERIENCE

Salt Lake Film Society, Salt Lake City, UT — Front of House Staff/Development Assistant

MAY 2015 - PRESENT

Trained team of 15+ Front of House staff on Union Procedures and Practices, and trained and managed team of 10+ volunteers on donor management in company database

CoAuthored Collective Bargaining Agreement while working on contract committee of 8 people to provide wage parity and industry standard practices to Front of House Staff Saved the nonprofit \$1000, initialized a retention program to track inventory Managed regular high pressure customer loads of up to a rate of 1500/hour

Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints, Salt Lake City, UT — Young Church Service Missionary

APRIL 2014 - APRIL 2016

Marathon tested 1000 digital media per hour assets during peak QC hours Product tested database and UI interface for Digital Media QC Programs Researched, presented and piloted a program for QC Mobile testing Quality Checked a variety of high volume websites organized in a task manager

Workforce QA, Salt Lake City, UT — Medical Review Officer Assistant

JUNE 2013 - MAY 2014

Reviewed thousands of documents for compliance standards

Performed routine indexing and data entry

Operated phone lines and directed calls for Medical Review processes

SKILLS

Front End

- Javascript
- React
- HTML 5
- CSS

Back End

- Node.js
- Express
- Mongo
- MongoDB

Other Skills

- Git
- JSON
- Adobe Premiere
- Adobe Audition

- AV Technician
- Public Speaking
- Management

EDUCATION AND CERTIFICATIONS

- Full Stack Javascript Web Development V School 2018
- IATSE Live Event Technician Certification 2019
- BS Economics Southern Utah University 2012